snowflakecomputing.com 2017-10-28

# Privacy Policy | Snowflake

**SNOWFLAKE**  
**ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY**

**Last Updated: 11/08/2016**  
This Policy explains how your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed via  
the web site [www.snowflake.net](http://www.snowflake.net/) (the “Site”). This Policy does not apply to the data that  
our customers store on the Snowflake Service (the “Service”), even if that data includes  
personal information of our customers or their end users. The provisions of the  
customer’s agreement with Snowflake govern customer data uploaded to the Service.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We collect information about you in various ways when you use the Site. We collect personal information you provide to us. For example, we collect your name, email address, postal address, phone number and other information you provide via the Site when you submit inquiries or request more information about our products or services. When you visit our Site, some information is automatically collected. For example, when you visit our Site your computer’s operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, and the website you visited before our site are logged automatically. We also collect information about your usage and activity of the Site.

  * **Cookies**.​ We may automatically collect information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Site and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Site.
  * **Web Beacons**.​ We may collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used via the Service or in our emails. We use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.
  * **Local Shared Objects**.​ We may use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or to display content based upon what you view on our Site to personalize your visit. Third party partners provide certain features on our Site and display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity using Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and way in which data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser usually will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for certain Flash cookies click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118>

From time to time, we may obtain information about you from third party sources, such as public databases, resellers and distributors, joint marketing partners, social media platforms, as well as from other third parties. Examples of the information we may receive from other sources include: account information, page-view information, and contact information from some business partners with which we operate co-branded events, services, marketing campaigns or joint offerings; search results and links, including paid listings (such as sponsored links); and credit history information from credit bureaus.

**Third Party Advertisements**

We may also use third parties to serve ads on the Site. Certain third parties may automatically collect information about your visits to this and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, and the browser you use to visit our Site. They do this using cookies, clear gifs, or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage of the Site tracked by these third parties. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or clear gifs in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

**THIRD PARTY APPLICATIONS**

We may link to certain third party websites and applications, such as Facebook. In those circumstances, your use of the Site will be subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, whether you are required to click through or otherwise. In addition, the third party website may also impose its own terms and conditions and privacy policies on your activities on their Site. HOWEVER YOU ACCESS OUR SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY AND COMPLY WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE SNOWFLAKE TERMS OF USE AND WAIVE ANY OBJECTION TO THE ENFORCEABILITY THEREOF WITH RESPECT TO YOUR USE OF THE SITE.

**USE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We use personal information collected via the Site for purposes described in this Policy.  
For example, we may use your information to:

  * operate and improve our Site, products, and services;
  * understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience and  
enjoyment using our Site, products, and services;
  * process and deliver contest entries and rewards;
  * respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * communicate with you about our products and services and to provide products and services you request;
  * to send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * link or combine it with other personal information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service. Snowflake may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries.

**SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We do not share your personal information with third parties other than as follows:

  * with your consent, for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies;
  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work for us and need access to your information to do that work;
  * to (i) comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect our rights and property and that of our agents, customers, members, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use or (iii) in an emergency to protect the personal safety of any person;
  * in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition, or dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets to another company.

We may also share aggregated or deidentified information.

**SNOWFLAKE ON DEMAND**

We make a self-service version of the Snowflake service available through the Site (“Snowflake On Demand”). When you register to use Snowflake On Demand, we collect your personal information and credit card information. Our use of the personal information you provide during registration for Snowflake On Demand is subject to this Privacy Policy. If you provide your credit card information during registration for Snowflake On Demand, you agree that we may share that information with our third-party service providers (including third-party payment processors and billing providers). Your use of Snowflake On Demand is subject to the Snowflake On Demand Terms of Service, not the Snowflake.net Terms of Use or any other terms.

We also make Snowflake On Demand available through the AWS Marketplace. If you provide your personal information to us during your registration for Snowflake On Demand through the AWS Marketplace, our use of the personal information you provide is subject to this Privacy Policy. Snowflake On Demand provided through the AWS Marketplace is subject to the Snowflake On Demand Terms of Service, not the Snowflake.net Terms of Use or any AWS terms.

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We take reasonable steps to help protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

**YOUR INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES**

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from us by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations. You may also send requests about your contact preferences and changes to your information including requests to opt-out of sharing your personal information with third parties by emailing [privacy@snowflake.net](mailto:privacy@snowflake.net).

Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Service. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Site visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

**California Users: Your California Privacy Rights**.

In addition, California’s “Shine the Light” law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the businesses’ practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you wish to find out about any rights you may have under California Civil Code section 1798.83, you may notify us in writing at [privacy@snowflake.net](mailto:privacy@snowflake.net).

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

We may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the “Last Updated” date above.

**QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at [privacy@snowflake.net](mailto:privacy@snowflake.net).
